"Gi"
It's a woman, all right!
More like a girl.
What's with that get-up?
Is she cryin' in there?
Hey! Eyes up here, brat!
Women don't belong on the battlefield!
We wanna see your face, you idiot!
Lady tactician, my ass...
You people killed my little brother
in that war two years back.
Hell, the Hi Shin Force killed
my big brother just last year!
And since you're their tactician,
you basically killed them yourself.
Right? Hey!
Are you even listenin', you little shit?!
You killed my big brother, too.
And my cousin!
He had little kids, man.
His whole family's out on the street!
Don't you get it, you dumb broad?!
How're you gonna help 'em, huh?
Bring in more spears!
Stones! Let's stone her!
Hey! What are you doing?
Take the girl with you and get a move on!
Gai Mou's calling for her!
Tch...
All right, on your feet.
The time has come, girlie.
That Gai Mou is something, all right!
Make sure you come back alive, now!
Yeah, 'cause after Gai Mou, you've got
all the rest of us to look forward to!
And after that,
we'll torture you--to death.
All the Gi people you killed,
all their anguish...
We'll give you a good taste of their pain!
Ten
I guess we gotta go for broke:
We stage a night raid and rescue her.
Oh, uh, right.
Just have to do everything we can...
Right.
Don't be stupid.
Ga Ro!
I know she's a tactician and all,
but risking hundreds and thousands
of lives for just one person?
I'm sure you old-timers have grown
really close with Ka Ryo Ten.
When you've only known her
a couple years, though,
it's hard to swallow.
Besides, the moment
that woman hit the battlefield,
she--and everyone--
would have accepted the risks.
Shin...
We have Ka Ryo Ten to think about, true,
but we also need to look
at the big picture.
Lieutenant So Sui is badly hurt;
he'll be hard-pressed to
return to the front lines.
And now that we've
lost our tactician, too,
I just don't see how we
can defeat Gai Mou's army
and reach Go Hou Mei's
main camp in two days.
Storming their HQ in three days
at the same time as the Gyoku Hou
Force and Roku O Mi's army:
That's our sole strategy
for taking Choyou.
Our failure puts the other
two armies in dire straits,
even leading to defeat
for the Chin army here.
We need to act while we still can--
and send an envoy to General Tou
asking to abort the mission!
Abort...
...the mission?
And all because of us...
I hate to say it, but I think
it's a wise decision.
Shin, sir...
Shin...
Wait.
There's one thing we can try.
It's a long shot, though.
What is it, Kyou Kai?
When Ka Ryo Ten was abducted,
I captured what looked like
an enemy commander.
Eh?
Knowing she couldn't be rescued,
Ka Ryo Ten shouted to me.
"Get that man," she said.
Ka Ryo Ten did?!
But what would she...
She-- She didn't mean--
Yes:
a hostage exchange.
"Kai"
What a strange face.
You're prepared to
be tortured, to be killed.
Or so it seems--but you're not.
Why have you taken to the battlefield?